<resources>
    <string name="app_name">5 Elements of Numbers</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email </string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password </string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">5 Elements of Numbers</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="userEmail">android.studio@android.com</string>


      <string name="root_number_1">A master of wisdom, an a born leader who like to takes charge.
    It is an intellectual, independent and masculine number. Person has the flair for acquiring wisdom.</string>
    <string name="root_number_2">Person is skillful and has a pleasant personality.
    It is a feminin number</string>
    <string name="root_number_3">Person has an active, warm, affectionate, and forward-looking personality.
    At times, they can exhibit a "happy-go-lucky" attitude. Person has a clear, focused mind and
    usually knows what he/she wants. They can be expressive, joyful, compassionate, and charismatic.</string>

    <string name="root_number_4">Person is a learned individual who is artistic and usually excels in examinations.
    They normally have high aspirations, and have a passion for lifelong learning. They are usually solid
    like a rock and can be stubborn at times</string>
    <string name="root_number_5">Person has a very strong character and is usually born with strong leadership traits.
        This person is charismatic and usually in a position above many. They have a strong instinct for things
        (intuitive) and have a hardworking nature, will usually achieve success in later part of life
    </string>
    <string name="root_number_6">Person is a survival who controls wealth and prosperity well. They tend to have
        good manners and are generally, loyal, loving, charming, creative, and have expensive taste. They usually
        do well in careers such as educaion, artistic works, and religion, and can be a popular figure in society.
        They are also a charismatic, caring, thoughtful and homely person.

    </string>
    <string name="root_number_7">Person is very skillful and detail-oriented when handling matters.
    They seldom forget those who had helped them before. A person is full of passion and love, charisma,
    charm, intelligence and appreciates gratitude. At thimes, their passion for love and romance
    may be on a high side. They tend to be more spiritual, to have a philosophical nature, and
    like to give "words of wisdom" to others.</string>
    <string name="root_number_8">Person is usually quiet, conservative and passive with a lively,
    enduring and perseverance nature</string>
    <string name="root_number_9">Person is usually optimistic, enthusiastic, and open-minded.</string>
    <string name="show_hidden_number">Show Hidden Number</string>
    <string name="hide_hidden_number">Hide Hidden Number</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">Main3Activity</string>
</resources>
